It is not a problem.
It is time duty.
What is the yellow or space?
Notice of information.
What is this?
This is the same. You have the same screen information in the same card.
How do we assume?
This information is the same.
How would you know if the information is in the card?
It is time duty.
And  beregistration.
They must have taken just one breath in front of their born is 1,2,3,4, 1.
Government spews law enforcementů
It would be a shame if  laying down the world in front in front of government spews law enforcement team.
Nobody actually lives even if they are known under the ire of the ire.
Unfortunately, ire is spread.
Those ire people in general arla have завdar met.
Let's go to the main topic.
Oh my god!
There are many complexes.
Let's see.
Floating to fixed.
And the low notes are floating to fixed.
It's simple.
Let's go to the next one.
What is this?
You have to change the rate.
But the vapor rate doesn't change automatically.
That's different.
If you have more civil,
you can go to the bank
and tell them that you have more civil,
change the rate or else I will go to you.
Then you change the rate.
This is also intelligence.
To save money.
You can say that
if you take so much of your civil,
you will get a loan.
But you have to increase it.
Benchmarks.
Some people give benchmarks.
MCLR.
Marginal Cost of Lending Rate.
This is a vapor rate benchmark.
This is MCLR benchmark.
This is also a benchmark.
You can shift the benchmark.
Generally people don't do it.
But there is an option.
Vapor rate is the ultimate.
Fixed rates are mostly MCLR.
Fixed rates are risky.
What is the full form of MCLR?
Marginal Cost of Lending Rate.
Who decides this?
The marginal cost of the bank
is the rate of lending.
Then they cut the marginal cost.
They take that.
You don't borrow, do you?
No, I don't.
There are many such cases.
The rate of libor.
London...
Institute of...
Of rate.
They take out the libor
and do the iBOR.
Mumbai.
They take out the rates of the banks.
They take out the benchmarks.
They take out the iBOR.
There is a private...
There is a bank of their own
and there is also an ABI.
There is a standardised
private market.
They don't judge it.
What is the customer's risk?
It is the cost of sleep.
I don't even know this.
Where is it?
What is it?
It is simple.
There are some things
This needs to be a lot simpler.
There is a legal language.
Somewhere it should be like
there are
3 to 4 ways bank calculate rates.
Either they depend on
RBI or
they have a consortium
of private banks
or they have their own individual
calculation.
Usually RBI
is most preferred and most
common. If you
want these type of facilities
you should go for this type
of.
Should feel like an advice
coming from a lawyer
instead of
just technical terms and legal
words.
What is 5%?
What is it?
I need a calculation
here.
This does not have a calculation.
No, you have to show
how an overdue is made.
I want to know
should I overdue after missing
And how much money should I overdue?
And how much charge should I get?
And
how many days
should I send notice?
And how many days
should I get a collection agency?
I don't know.
I am just saying that I have missed
You should know something.
There is no monitoring value.
It doesn't matter.
Show me the calculation.
Calculation means
I can put the data on top of
my calculation.
Why?
You should
not
No, bro.
How did you get 2%?
You have written the annum.
But I put a total amount in the next month.
I have not used
the money for an annum.